Come on, yeah.
- Yeah!
- Flip your head back.
Oh, fuck!
- I wanna taste it.
- You wanna taste it?
My little gold-painted whore!
Yeah? You wanna?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you
fuck my little gold pussy.
- I wanna cum on that face of yours, baby.
- Yeah.
- That little gold face, right now, baby.
It all came off.
I was naked by the end of it.
OK, focus.
Keep going.
Open your mouth, baby.
Taste it.
I'm coming.
Oh, yeah.
Cut.
That was amazing, guys.
- Oh, dude. That gold paint was brilliant.
- Wasn't it?
- You're a genius, mate.
- Thanks.
Could I get my
phone please, babe,
so that I can take some
photos before I get cleaned up?
You're so stunning.
- Here.
- Cheers.
Hey, dude, did you get
my blinged-up gold dick?
- Yeah.
- Kinda cool.
I was worried
about that, actually.
I don't want to get
another yeast infection.
No, it should be fine.
That was edible paint.
Right, cup of tea?
Good, you're awake.
It's too early.
No, I'm late, actually.
It's my second week, so I don't
want to fuck it up straight away.
You're too cool
for school, baby.
Yeah. I uploaded Angels Go Anal
and Niagara Falls Pussy Squirt.
Lizzie emailed that she'll
be here with Amy at 5:30.
So, you need to pick
them up at the station, OK?
Dad?
Dad, what do you need to do?
Pick…
Pick the ladies
up at the station.
OK. Good.
A-D-H-D.
- Sorry.
- You're late, and you're up next.
The best excuse for being
late is being worth the wait.
Ethan and Tess.
So, Alec,
you care to share
your topic of choice?
- Addiction?
- Sorry?
Addiction?
Drug and alcohol
abuse are already taken.
Internet addiction?
Yeah, not bad.
Internet addiction is
a growing problem.
It's not a recognised
mental disorder just yet,
but they are in the
process of researching it.
So, it's a very current subject.
But internet addiction has different
types, so let's try and narrow it down.
What other types
can you think of?
Gaming?
A way to lose yourself
to a new reality.
Or for some, a way to
avoid a deeper problem.
What other types
can you think of?
I can think of two or three,
off the top of my head.
Porn?
At what point does a hobby
become an addiction, miss?
Well, porn addiction often
comes hand-in-hand with anxiety.
Hand-in-hand, yeah?
Anxiety and social
maladjustment.
So, that doesn't sound
like a very fun hobby to me.
Have you got a
partner to work with?
I haven't got that sorted yet.
Oi, Alec.
Go for porn, mate,
and I'll be your partner.
Yeah, I'll go for online
porn addiction, miss.
I would like to put myself
forward as Alec's partner, miss.
I bet you would.
But I think for this one, we're going to
have a male and female perspective.
So, which of the girls hasn't
been partnered up with?
Nina!
No, miss. I'd much rather work
with one of the lads on this, please.
Porn addiction.
Alec and Nina.
Let's be creative with
this one, shall we?
It's a multi-media assignment.
Try and make it interesting for
your fellow classmates, yeah?
Right, who's next?
So, how do you want to do this?
I don't know.
Well, my place is a no-go.
My mum's in the midst
of this crazy renovation.
It's really messy.
Look, she has me painting
all the walls in the living room.
Yeah, my place isn't
a good idea either,
because my dad doesn't like having
people around when he's working.
He works from home, so…
Here.
Where are we going?
I'll take you to my favourite
spot and we can talk there.
After you.
No, you go.
Fine.
- Am I walking too fast?
- No, no.
Welcome to my woman-cave.
We're talking porn
in a pussy cave?
Not if you're gonna be a dick!
No, it… It's really
nice, actually.
Have you ever heard
of female-friendly porn?
Yeah.
- Do you watch it?
- Not really.
I find it weird that
something like that is a thing.
Like, why would that even exist if
the regular shit wasn't so alienating?
Well…
What do you like?
I prefer not getting fed sexuality
through the experience of others.
I'd rather find my
own with someone.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey.
Nearly done, mate.
Start with promo pics and
special requests for Lizzie.
We'll start shooting
straight after.
Follow me down.
Can you arch a bit, and
then I can see…? Yeah.
Yeah.
That's great.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah.
Yes.
All right.
- Lose the underwear?
- OK.
All right.
So,
your arse towards
me, and the camera.
Sure.
Yeah.
This good?
Yeah. And then can
you look back, like eyes?
Can you spread them a bit more?
Yes, I can.
And stick your tongue out.
Yeah.
You're getting so good at this.
I know.
OK, yeah.
Great. Are you ready for
some special requests?
Yeah, what have they got for us?
They want me to smoke?
Yeah.
From your arsehole.
How is that even sexy?
I don't even
know if I can do it.
Try.
Have you got a lighter?
All of them.
- All of them?
- Yeah.
Are they even gonna fit?
OK.
Don't burn me.
Yeah.
Monsieur.
Chef's finest.
Cheers.
Looking good, buddy.
There's no filming
this weekend, right?
I'm supposed to work on an
assignment with a girl from school, so…
What?
Stop.
Who is she?
She's not my type.
Type?
Every woman's unique, mate.
Uniquely batshit crazy.
I mean, look at these
two loons, bless 'em.
No such thing as
a perfect bird, mate.
That's a good thing, right?
Cos then we don't
have to be perfect either.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get
shit done here.
Got ya.
My boy's brilliant.
He's the bollocks.
All done and uploaded.
Well, you're welcome.
Mate, I'm sorry.
Come sit with your dad.
Please?
OK.
I'm sorry, kiddo.
All these bills are just
doing my swede in.
We need more birds.
And more downloads.
And a career change?
Funny.
You know, I was thinking
if we could maybe, erm
hold off telling people
out here what we do?
Has something happened?
No. No, no.
I just want to make some
friends first, that's all.
Oh, dude, you will.
I promise you,
you will. I swear.
Promise.
Get the cutlery
and bowls out, dude.
You have a visitor, mate.
Thanks for not showing.
- We said Sunday.
- Yeah, and it is Sunday.
- Fuck!
- Yeah, fuck me!
I sat there like an
idiot for ages, Alec.
I tried to call you as well.
No, I'm really sorry.
I'm such a fucking idiot.
Is anyone hungry?
I'm making soup.
I'm sorry, my phone
must have died.
Yeah, it did.
I'm really sorry.
You're not forgiven.
This belongs to that weirdo.
I can use it
whenever I want, so…
Is he a photographer?
Yeah. Yeah, he is, yeah.
- Shall we start the assignment?
- Yeah.
"Being In Total Control Honey".
When was the last time
you were called a bitch?
Last night.
Bitch.
Slut.
Whore.
Cunt.
Cum dumpster.
Fuck doll.
Whoa!
Cunt, cum dumpster…
Bimbo.
Pussy.
Fuckmeat.
Fuck me?
Fuckmeat?
OK, let's do the men.
Big daddy?
Strong.
Have a wheeze on it, if
you want. Promise not to tell.
She's just saying goodbye
cos her mum called, so…
Yeah, I've got to
go paint - again.
Renovating?
Does she have a good handyman?
Handywoman, actually.
My mum just works with
female contractors, so…
You're shitting me?
Positive discrimination.
She's quite strong on that.
You're telling me
you only have a bunch
of birds in to do your
plumbing and shit?
Yeah.
Oi, Alec.
Come here.
How you doing, man, you good?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- You smoke?
- Yeah.
I've only got my last one.
Lucky boy.
Cheers.
So, with this assignment
do you guys watch porn together?
- Yeah?
- No.
Is it inspiring?
Thanks for the smoke, mate.
Oi, hang on, mate.
Oi!
I'm just saying
it's a smart idea,
choosing that topic.
Getting to watch porn all day
with Miss Lunachick Riot Girl.
It's the best when they're not
into it and you make them watch.
And they're like,
"Oh, that's disgusting!"
But they're actually
getting off on it.
You can see it in
their eyes, they can't
stop fucking
watching, it's brilliant!
Why didn't I think of that?
I guess you're just
not that smart, mate.
What was that, mate?
Get off me.
I was trying to be nice!
Hey, lads. Break it up.
That's enough.
All right, let's dip.
Did you see that, man? I should
have fucking knocked him out.
Alec!
Get on. I'll take you home.
I'm going for a walk.
I'll join you.
All right, come on.
Yeah, my mum died when I was 12.
Shit! I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I hardly see my dad.
He lives in Morocco.
Yeah, there was a time I didn't
see much of my dad, either.
After they split, my mum
took me back home with her.
Why do you keep
moving away from me?
I'm not.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
OK then.
Let's try this thing my
mum does with her clients.
Clients?
She's a life coach.
OK.
Are you good?
Perfect.
How about now?
Couldn't be better.
You can take two
steps if you want.
Are you still comfortable?
Cheers.
Can I come in for a pee?
Thing is, when my
dad's at work,
he doesn't really like to
have people around.
I'll be literally two
seconds and that's it.
Do you really think your dad
wants me to piss myself, Alec?
Dad, I'm home! Nina's here.
What's up, buttercup?
Hi, do you have
a toilet I could use?
- I really need to go.
- Yeah.
Just through there,
back and to the left.
Thank you.
- A quick piss, and she's off, OK?
- Of course.
Don't provoke anything.
- Oh, fuck!
- What?
- Butt plugs in the toilet sink.
- Fuck!
I'm mucking about.
It's all good, all clear.
Jesus Christ!
Do you think she wipes?
For fuck's sake!
Drip dry.
So, what kind of shoot is this?
Nightwear, like pyjamas.
That is so cool.
Yeah, that's Lizzie's.
One of Dad's regular models.
Like it?
You can have it, if you want.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Tell you what, bang it
on, let's have a gander.
Oh, yeah!
That looks awesome.
Thank you, I really like this.
Yeah.
Hey, why don't
you take a photo for Lizzie?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Is that all right?
- Yeah, that's fine.
- OK.
How about down
here? Better lighting.
Could you get out
of the shot, then?
Yep. Sorry.
You don't smile. That's nice.
OK, done.
Show her your snaps, mate.
No, don't, because I'll cringe.
Thank you for the
shirt, though. It's so cool.
I'll see you tomorrow
at school, right?
Yeah.
I think she's into you.
She's not.
- Morning, Cathy.
- Morning, miss.
- Morning.
Alec?
Yes?
Could you come to
my office for a moment?
I understand that there's been an
incident between yourself and Jamie.
I was hoping that you might
tell me a bit more about that.
No, I mean it was nothing, so…
You know, anything
that we discuss in
here can remain
between you and me.
No, I'm good, I'm good.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
OK.
I'm just going to give
your dad a quick call.
So he can join us, and
we're all on the same page.
Hello?
Oh, hello. Mr Moore?
Mr Dylan Moore?
Who is this?
This is Mrs Bennett.
Headmistress of
Bright-cliff College.
Who?
Mrs Bennett?
Headmistress of
Bright-cliff College.
What time is it?
8:47, Mr Moore. I'm
sorry if I woke you.
Fucking hell.
Excuse me, Mr Moore. Yes?
Nina.
Miss Evergreen says I
can't attend class like this.
I DIDN'T COME FROM YOUR
RIB YOU CAME FROM MY VAGINA
But that's an important
message, don't you think?
Hold on. Apologies, Mr Moore…
Mr Moore?
Dad's not much of
a morning person.
Night shifts.
No problem. I can call him later,
when it's more convenient for him.
You two, go back to class.
I don't want you missing
any more of it. And, Nina, yes.
It's an important message.
Have you got anything
else underneath?
No.
Then I suggest you
pop along to lost property
and fish something out.
I think that
complements the uniform.
I should get Lizzie to print one
out with "I wish I was a bitch" on it.
Yeah, I love that.
OK, turn around.
Oh, sorry.
"Only the blind can truly
see past sex and beauty."
That's what my mum
used to tell my dad.
Until he brought
home a Braille Playboy.
Which made her laugh.
She loved touching Braille.
Do you still have it?
Dad hasn't let anyone
touch it since Mum died, so…
You can turn around now.
Hey, baby boy.
What are you doing here?
Oh, your dad was talking
to the headmistress.
He's waiting for you in the car.
Alec.
Babe, hold up!
- Hey, kiddo.
- Why the fuck would you bring her?
I had to pick her up from the
station. It's on the way, mate.
Why would you wear those?
You're not on fucking camera.
I'm breaking them
in, if you must know.
It's not like I was expecting to
be running a race now, was it?
The fuck was that?
They think you're a slut.
That's not a compliment.
I don't give a fuck
what they think.
It's taken me a long time to
be comfortable with who I am
and what I do, and
what people think of me.
Don't try and shame me.
Seriously, it's fucked-up.
Dude.
We're good.
I got your
back, you got mine.
Don't make them feel
like you're shit. You're not.
And never,
never feel the need to have
to turn on family or friends.
You get me?
I love you.
Let them fucking judge!
Right?
We're not part of
their fucking club!
We're the Lone Wolf Club!
And let's hear us howl!
- Oi, oi, Alec.
- All right, mate?
- Where's the hottie?
- How should I know?
I don't keep her
on a fucking lead.
I bet she'd like you to.
Hey, Nina!
Did you get to
meet Alec's new girlfriend?
Why do you always
talk shit, Jamie?
No one cares what
you have to say.
Sounds like someone
could use a deep-throat fuck.
Or do you prefer pussy?
- Like your mum?
- You're such a dick.
Oi!
Think we wouldn't find this?
Oh, you fucking got it, yeah.
Yeah, we found
out about your dad.
- Quite a movie star!
- You dirty little cunt slut.
- Hey, Nina.
- Don't look.
- This is the best part.
Where she starts to gag, look.
Fucking take it deeper!
- Look, Nina, you can learn from this.
- You're so fucking nasty.
Fucking look at me.
Come on, mouthfuck me.
You fucking love
it when you choke!
Yeah? Choke, you
dirty fucking bitch!
Nasty, baby. You're
so fucking nasty.
Alec!
Oh, fuck!
He's not here, he's
in London tonight, so…
If you're not comfortable,
I get it, it's fine.
But I'd… I'd really like…
like you to come in.
- Now you.
- No, no, that's fine.
Painkillers will do.
Don't take the blue
ones, though, yeah?
That's very funny.
And very old-school, actually.
Cos he takes
Cialis for hard wood.
It just works faster, I think.
Oh, shit.
No, that's probably my mum.
I'm not answering
that. More child labour.
You can stay over, if you want.
What, in that tiny bed of yours?
Well…
That looks better
on you than me.
So, have you slept here before?
No, never.
No.
I was just wondering, actually.
Was your mum
OK with what your dad does?
Did that cause the split?
Oh, erm… no.
No, they actually…
They actually met on set.
That's quite a first date.
I don't want to go all the way.
We can do other stuff.
Can we just…?
Can you just look at me?
I like looking at you.
Alec.
Up here.
Oh, fuck.
I'm so sorry.
Nina?
Let's just go.
Nina!
Nina, please.
Can I take a step?
Can I take another one?
Another one?
I'm sorry.
At least we know
where the boy is now.
Hello, baby.
Your dad's been
looking for you all day.
We were meant to shoot.
Are you OK?
What have you done
to your pretty face?
Sexy cut!
Yeah, he's here. He's all right.
You're cute when you're drunk.
- I'm not drunk.
- You're not drunk?
Let's have a drink, then.
And sway. Hips. Left and right.
I'm sorry.
Just give me a minute, OK?
I'm ready to shoot.
Get your jumper off.
Yeah, there he is.
Welcome.
Let's have a look there.
Sexy, eh?
You scared me
for a moment there.
Not picking up your phone, no
one knowing where you were.
So, you were worried about me?
Well,
you've never gone AWOL
the night before a shoot, have you?
I always thought
nothing scared you.
You know I fainted
when you were born?
Really?
It's gross, innit? Birth.
All that blood and
placenta and stuff.
Your little fingers
clenched together.
It seemed so unfair, you
having to come out so small.
Dependent.
Fragile as hell.
You were screaming.
I was holding you in my arms…
I started to cry.
And the moment I started crying
you just stopped.
And you just stared at me.
And it was just you and me.
- Just you and me.
- Yeah.
Morning, Casanova.
Get that down your gullet.
It'll do wonders
for your hangover.
What, blended frog?
There's plenty
of fruit in there, too.
Go on, neck it back. One go.
Yeah, good boy!
So, erm…
I've got this new
girl coming in later.
Do you, erm…
Do you reckon
you'll be up for it?
Well, does she have
experience or no experience?
No experience, but
she's a
luscious little thing.
Perky tits, great arse.
She's got alabaster
translucent skin,
rosy little cheeks, so she probably
gets all flushed when she comes.
If you're not up for it, though,
no presh.
But,
you know, I can reschedule.
Might be a bit tricky,
though, cos you know
we're super low on content.
Yeah, no, I'll be fine.
I'll be fine once
the frog kicks in.
Ribbit.
I'm gonna go get prepped.
There you go.
Great. Thank you.
OK, ready when you are.
Rose.
It's a beautiful
name, by the way.
Thanks.
I'm named after my nana.
Best not think about
her right now, yeah?
Oh, yeah babe.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, I’m so hard.
So fucking deep
inside you, yeah?
Let me see your
cheeks get all rosy, baby.
You love it, don't you? Yeah?
Tell Daddy you love it.
Fuck, come on!
Tell me you love it.
Come on!
Tell me you love it!
Come on, baby, say something.
Can you fucking
say something, babe?
Let's try something
different, OK?
Could you maybe
lay on your back?
Yeah.
And your leg, can you stretch
it to the side of your head?
- Like this?
- Yeah.
Is that OK?
Let's try that.
All right, let's hear you
this time, yeah, babe?
So we know you're enjoying it?
I've always been quiet.
Oh, that's nice when you're
back home in bed, babe.
But, erm…
Civilians need audio, yeah?
We've gotta hear your porn roar.
- You've seen porn, yeah?
- Yeah.
So, you know how
the birds are all like,
"Yeah! Come on!
Fucking give it to me!"
Shouting and screaming
and hollering, yeah?
- Right, you rolling?
- Yeah.
OK, stop.
You can put your leg
down for a minute, OK?
Just… Just relax.
What?
Why can't we try
something different?
Something different?
That'd be jamming four
cocks in her arse instead of two.
Everything else has been done.
I say let her be quiet, if
that's how she enjoys sex.
Could we… maybe
touch a bit more?
I like it when I'm
touched, like here.
- OK.
- That would help me make more sounds.
Is hugging and kissing OK?
Kisses on my neck
really turn me on.
And licking my ear
makes my whole body tingle.
Sorry, babe,
we need
space to capture the action.
It's all about penetration.
Hands just get in the way.
Well, no, cos I could
zoom in on her face,
then that will be all about
what she really feels.
Cos if you touch
her where she likes it,
we'll see
all that on her face.
You can guide him, right?
Yeah? That would
be good to watch.
It's not an art project.
Or a love affair.
It's business.
So, when you want
caressing, I want…
spanking!
And a bit of hair-pulling.
And some hardcore fucking.
We're making porn
here, people, not love.
Could you just…?
Thanks.
Sorry.
She's getting dressed.
Getting dressed, babe, yeah?
I don't think this is for me.
You know what? I'd
bugger off up the art school.
Bit of nude modelling, that'll
sort you out, nice and quiet.
- You don't need to be rude.
- I'm not being rude.
- I'm just being honest.
- Now that we're being honest…
You're a pretty lousy fuck.
Oh, it was worth a try.
I thought she'd be up for it.
Met her in the chemist.
The fucking chemist?
So, you're just picking them
up off the streets now, yeah?
Erm, listen…
I'd like my money.
Now.
Cash.
As promised.
Babe, the material's unusable.
I really need the money.
We all need the money, babe.
It simply wasn't good enough.
No, I really need it.
Can we at least
give her something?
We're not running
a charity here.
Look, babe, I'm
still full of junk.
If you want to come back in
and have another bash,
sure, absolutely,
let's go for it.
But we need some
useable footage.
Here's 15.
- Dude, really?
- That's all I've got at the moment.
- I'm very sorry.
- Thanks.
Fuck off!
Keep the change, yeah?
Nice.
Lovely.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Is Nina home?
Oh, you must be Alec.
Yeah.
It's nice to finally meet you.
I'm Julia.
Nina!
Alec's here!
Is it
true that
you only work
with female contractors?
When possible, yeah.
So,
are all your clients
only women as well?
Come on, then.
Go back in.
My dad, he would never…
you know, ask for help.
He likes fighting
his problems alone.
He's pretty fearless.
My guess is
that he's brave.
Because no one's fearless.
- Let me go upstairs and just see…
- No.
I should go.
Lastly,
Alec and Nina.
How are things going
with your project?
You're the only ones I haven't
received any updates from.
Is there anything we
can help you with?
Wait, Nina.
Nina, wait.
Nina.
Being In Total Control Honey (B.i.t.c.h.)
Wait.
I WISH I WAS A BITCH
Is this your man cave?
So, we're talking
porn in a manhole?
You'll like it.
How is this a good
place for us to work?
It's up here.
Close your eyes.
No, I'm all right.
Just trust me.
You'll like it, I promise.
OK.
You're making me feel up girls.
No, it's just…
It's just the interviews.
They don't describe
the pictures or anything.
Close your eyes.
What's up, mate?
What's all this?
Oh, it's, erm…
It's merch, mate.
Merchandise.
My signature cock.
Now, when I DP a chick,
both cocks can be mine.
"You are the proud owner
of Wade Savage's cock
the dick that has
launched a thousand loads
and has been inside
countless hotties.
And which can now
be inside you."
Not tested on animals.
Fifty quid a pop.
I'm sure they'll fly right
off the fucking shelf.
Why not? I mean,
look at this beauty.
Had a ton of requests.
Yeah? Like five?
It's just so
incredibly accurate.
I mean, look at it!
That
beautiful penis in your
hand there, that gorgeous manhood
it's always put food on the table
for you, a roof over your head.
I'm pretty sure Mum did.
That's not fair.
I thought we're
a great team, no?
I think you're brilliant.
Best operator I've ever
had by far, you know that.
You know what's
important, you get me.
I know things are tough at
the moment but, honestly,
I've been putting
a lot of thought
into this and how
we can stand out.
Yeah, but VR porn. I've
told you that, VR and games.
I told you that all along.
We haven't got the money
for that at the moment,
you know that.
But I promise you, I've got
some great things up my sleeve.
We're gonna talk about it, yeah?
OK.
But right now,
I want to know what's
going on with you.
You walked in here
all weird and radiating.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I knew it. I knew it!
That's great!
My boy enjoying
the good things in life!
- I'm proud of you, man.
- Yeah.
Well, it's not what
you think anyway, so…
Hang on!
Why don't you and Nina
get down the boozer
tomorrow night?
First drink's on me.
Take it, it's yours.
Bit of testosterone!
I like it.
Yeah. En garde, monsieur.
I challenge you to a cock fight.
Oh, monsieur, you
fight well with your cock!
Your big, beautiful
Wade Savage cock.
Ah, fuck!
Oh, shit! That's
Nina. She's early.
Get dressed, OK?
Come on, guys,
please get dressed.
I'd take her straight up to
your room, if I were you, mate.
It's far too hot in
here for clothes, baby.
- Hi.
Oh, they've finished filming.
The cameraman just
left, so they're… unwinding.
I thought they only film
when you're at school.
Oh, yeah. There were
some scheduling problems.
I'm not an idiot.
I don't think you're an idiot.
Stop bullshitting me then.
OK.
Do you have the camera?
Oh, yeah.
I'll meet you in my room.
Can I just come with you?
OK, yeah.
What's up, buttercup? Come
and meet the famous Lizzie.
Hello, baby.
Oh, my God, it's so
nice to finally meet you.
Why didn't you guys tell
me how beautiful she was?
Honestly, you are just… perfect.
I can see why he's got
a big fat crush on you.
Wait, I've got
something for this one.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, you should come with me.
Girl time.
Don't worry about it, mate.
She'll be fine.
I thought you might like to see
my latest drop.
You can choose one.
You don't have to,
but I just thought
you might want one.
But make sure to
tell your friends, right?
I need to sell them,
I've got so many.
OK.
You know, peeing is
one of the healthiest
things you can do
after you have sex.
OK.
Good advice that.
Where do you get
your quotes from?
I mean, everywhere really.
Most of them are mine though.
That's cool.
Alec told me you're not
really a fan of our industry.
I get it.
But…
you might be interested to know
that I've never felt as accepted
anywhere in this
world as I do right here.
And acceptance is a
really hard thing to come by.
You'll notice that
as you get older.
That looks really
cute, by the way.
Thank you.
I just feel like
most women are eager to please.
And porn, that takes
it to the next level
and I don't see how that
benefits us in the long run.
I mean, you're not
entirely wrong, babe.
But let's be honest here.
We all know what it's like to
smile along with something
we don't really want to do
or agree with something that
we don't actually agree with.
Even you.
I know you've got your whole
feminist exterior and all that,
but I know you know
what I'm talking about.
We suffer alone.
And we smile in public.
And
the porn industry
is absolutely no different.
And, yeah, hardcore stuff
can be hard on the girls.
But again, porn
didn't create that.
Patriarchy.
Patriarchy did.
You know I've never
once seen Dylan get shit
for what he does.
And I get shit all the time.
Yet he's the producer.
Maybe it's cos he's like…
I don't know, learnt
how to not give a fuck.
I haven't quite
mastered that yet.
That's Dylan.
It's sized up though.
Don't tell him
that I told you that.
He'd be mortified.
It's well fun to have
a dick sometimes.
Do you fuck him
with his own cock?
There is no way that man would
ever let a penis
near his arsehole,
even if it was his own replica.
He does like getting
his arse eaten, though.
He's all like, "Oh, yeah,
babe! Lick it like a stamp!"
How emancipated of him.
Hey.
It's easy to be a feminist
from the sidelines.
But you're in a porn
producer's house.
Why don't you go confront him?
Start walking the walk a little
bit instead of just talking the talk.
What do you have in mind?
Try me.
Suck it.
I said suck it!
Yeah, I heard
you the first time.
Go on.
Be a good boy.
Well, if you want
me to be a good boy
you'll have to come
down on your knees, baby.
You come up to me, bitch.
What the fuck?
No!
Alec!
What the hell was that?
Was that your idea of
your feminist revenge?
Being the dick you
so fucking despise?
Why are you getting
involved in any of this?
You despise porn.
What do you
mean "get involved"?
I am involved.
The whole world
is involved
why do you think I'm
doing this assignment?
No, this is child's play.
You're barely
scratching the surface.
Enlighten me, then.
Enlighten your classmates,
since you know the real deal.
Real deal?
Behind the fantasy.
They'll never watch
porn the same way again.
Stop pushing your
activism shit on me.
You get a chance to do
something meaningful here,
You don't see how
beautiful that is?
This is my life
you're talking about.
Exactly, this is your life.
So, live it.
You think
that you've been hiding stuff,
but it's been hiding you instead.
I'm really hungry.
What?
Nothing.
It's just that
this…
This is nice.
Come on, you two.
Better late than never.
Right.
Well, if you want to
bung us a bit of cash,
I'll take it away
after, if you want.
Can I erm… just dump it in
the sea when I'm done with it?
Up to you, mate. It's yours now.
Holy fuck!
It's a beauty.
You ready?
Not really.
It's harmless.
- Right.
- Babe, you said you'd be up for it.
I'm paying you triple.
I know.
I know, Dylan. All right,
just give me a minute.
We are gonna crank
them downloads, mate.
Suck a tentacle.
Fuck off!
You've sucked
dirtier dicks than that.
Yeah, yours.
Are you getting anything, mate?
Can you open up?
I can't move now.
It's fucking glued to me.
This was such a bad idea!
Fucking hell!
Fuck, I can't see
anything. Can you open up?
Meanwhile, you
ain't even hard.
I know, babe.
He can shoot you
knocking one out.
I'll get back in
business with a Cialis.
Mate, can you
bang us over a pill?
This is fucking bonkers.
I'm so stuck.
Just let it slide over you.
Relax.
Babe, it's gorgeous.
Just relax.
Yeah.
Open your leg a bit for camera.
Just a little bit more.
Babe, relax.
It's fantastic.
You look fabulous.
You've been such
a trouper, baby,
but you've got to
control the shaking.
Just make it sexual, yeah?
Just hold on a bit longer.
We'll get one
more shot, darling.
I'll fuck you with it inside
you and we have got gold!
- Yeah, keep going.
- Fuck, I've cut.
- Why the fuck you cut?
- Fuck off!
I can't get it out.
Fuck!
Dylan, what the fuck?
Stop fucking filming!
What is wrong with you?
No, come on, hang on.
Get back in there, please.
Honestly, you can fuck off.
Are you fucking serious?
Don't look at me like that
I can fucking feel it!
I'm paying her good,
she agreed to do it.
It's a family business.
It's business!
You're such a fucking hypocrite.
All that bullshit about me being
the best operator you ever had.
It's cos I'm the only one who
puts up with your fucking shit!
I'm good at what I do,
but you don't
have a fucking clue.
Because if you did,
you'd want something
better for me than
this fucking shit!
Oh, fuck!
Alec.
Hi.
Are you OK?
I've just asked him that.
Mum?
What's wrong?
It's just my dad's such…
My dad's such a cunt!
And I don't really want to
spend the night there tonight.
Come inside.
Do you remember when
you were surprised at the age
kids see porn at
for the first time?
I was five.
Shit!
One time, when the door to our
home studio was
left open, I peeked in.
And no one was
watching me
because I never really had
a proper babysitter.
It was usually just
one of the girls on
set or a make-up artist
that would look after me when my
parents were doing a scene, but…
I remember the sounds.
It used to make me
think that my mum
was in some sort of pain.
I should probably keep this
kind of stuff to myself, right?
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah, see ya.
Wait, Alec.
I fucked up.
It shouldn't get between us.
You're the most
important thing in my life.
No mucking about.
Here.
Hi.
I want that.
Ow, wait!
What's that?
Oh. Oh, shit.
Sorry.
Look at me.
I love looking at you.
Here.
Close your eyes.
Just trust me.
OK.
Can I open them?
Nina?
That's what it feels like
when you won't look at me.
We're in the same room, but
I feel like you're just not there.
Just
do it really slowly.
OK.
Wait.
Wait, is that recording?
Fuck.
Did you turn it on?
No.
You must have, when you
sat on it, do you remember?
Oh, shit!
It doesn't matter,
we can erase it.
Shit.
Alec
come and give
us a hand, will you?
- I'll be right back.
- OK.
Hey, man.
Amy's coming down tomorrow
with a new bird.
What do you reckon, about 4:30?
I know it's tight
with school, but…
Nothing freaky this time.
I promise you, just regular.
I'm not doing this any more.
I know.
Are you watching it?
No, I was trying to
figure out how to erase it.
Do you want to watch it?
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
Just do it really slowly.
OK.
That wasn't…
It didn't
look like
anything it felt like.
I mean, it was good.
For you, too, was it?
I mean…
a lot of it was.
The start was really nice.
Really?
Really.
Hold on.